As we all travel across the
sea Raising our voices We
take in the beautiful blue
world Our spirits ready to
go Everybody rejoices Now
let's go get the sails all
yeah Here we are in between
the sea and the sky Ready
now for adventure We're
itching to try Get ready to
roam So all aboard now We're
set to go Set sail to the
ocean so deep Ready for a
truly grand adventure Well,
don't you think That sounds really
fun All this excitement Second
to none As we all travel across
the sea Raising our voices We take
in the beautiful blue world Our
spirits ready to go Everybody
rejoices Now let's go get the sales
yeah If there's something
that I just won't
ever forget It's the way that I felt when
our journey was set Now
I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud!
If this is a dream, I
don't want to wake up.
Taking a hot bath while the
waves gently rock the boat.
This is the life.
An office.
I have my very own doctor's office.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Got him!
Look!
We caught a cool shark!
Put it in! Put it in!
Put it in the fish
tank! Ha ha ha ha! Yeah!
Right in you! Oh!
Seems we have a new guest, a shark.
So, this room perfect or what?
The room's fine, but don't those
idiots know a shark's a bad idea?
Hurry up!
Let's go see it!
Yeah, the fish are gonna love this!
Hey! Hey!
Can you see the shark yet?
It's the one with the big horns!
Yes, it's an impressive specimen.
Unfortunately, it doesn't seem
to play very well with others.
What did you think was gonna happen?
Don't you know how the food
chain works, you idiot?
You stupid shark!
I'm gonna eat you for doing that!
Sanji, turn this bastard
into a barbecue dinner!
You can't barbecue everything.
This is a fresh fish we're talking about.
It could be sushi, or we could boil
it and add some spicy vinegar Miss.
Maybe even sharp to the corner.
Let's make all of them!
That was just what I needed.
Hey, there's something
floating in the ocean.
Let me see.
Where is it? There.
A barrel?
Huh?
I think it says treasure on it.
Hey, you're right.
Maybe you fell off a treasure ship.
Let's find out.
Treasure time!
Open it up and see what's inside!
Whatever it is, it's gonna be fine!
Pity!
It's probably just some old
booze and preserved food.
What?
You can't see inside!
How do you know?
Because it says a treasure
offering to the sea gods.
It's an old practice
called barrel drifting.
People pray for safe passage by making an
offering to the guardian
spirits of the sea.
So it's more about superstition
than actual treasure.
In other words we got our hopes up over
a barrel of sea trash whoa who says booze
is trash let's drink it what no that's
bad karma you'll be fine just say a little
prayer first i pray to know god sea or
otherwise alcohol stirred by the waves from
what i hear that improves
the taste oh yeah
let's find out all right then we'll make a
toast after you finish they say that you're
supposed to add a new offering and set
it adrift again for good luck okay who
cares open up so hey
god we're stealing your
booze now you're praying to god if i
remember you beat the crap out of god back on
skypea don't bother god's
a jerk prayer's over
here goes okay let me
see whoa what is that
Fireworks?
It sure is bright, huh?
What?
What's going on?
The booze flew in the
air, and then it blew up!
Looks like a signal flare.
You think that's it?
Guess the sea god didn't like
you messing with his stuff.
It could just be a prank, I suppose.
But if it's not...
If it's not...
Perhaps we've alerted someone, and
they're about to come looking for us.
Ah!
You mean the booze was a lie?
No, even worse, it was a trap, and
we set it off by opening the barrel.
Who knows what kind of horrible
people are going to come after us now?
Something isn't right.
I can feel it.
It's the air pressure.
The clouds are moving fast, too.
I'm looking all over the
place, but I don't see anyone.
Nothing here.
Everyone get into position.
We're going to escape south by southwest.
A huge storm is coming in five minutes!
I don't see anything, but
if you say it's coming,
I'll take your word for it
since you're the navigator.
By the way, what's our heading?
Two o 'clock, straight ahead!
No good.
We're getting straight headwinds.
The ship's gonna overturn!
Hey, the sun can handle this.
You know the trick. Oh, right.
Hey guys, raise the
sails! It's paddle time!
Yeah, okay!
I like the sound of that! Do it!
Soldier, dock system, channel zero!
Hula engines, paddle ship, study!
Goal!
Full speed!
We made it yeah it's nice we got out of the
storm and all but where the hell are we?
It shouldn't be night yet right so why
is it so dark and what's with this fog?
strange huh This is it
we paddled the sunny
straight into that sea
kokoro was talking about.
Geez I wasn't ready for this.
Oh wow.
So we're at Fishman Island already.
Not yet
Remember the sea of ghosts
That's right.
Be careful
You've heard of the
Florian Triangle, right?
You know, it's also called
the Devil's Triangle
Haunted sea where ships are swallowed
by the darkness without a trace.
On the ghost I can't wait shut
up why does everyone know about
this except me if this is some
kind of prank it's not funny.
Nah it's real and I
hear there's zombies and
skeletons too why are
you happy about this loop
You're letting your imagination
run wild stop trying to scare him.
Listen Usopp the truth of the
matter is every year over a
hundred ships vanish in these
waters without any explanation.
They say the sailor's souls stay on the
ships, wandering for all eternity. No!
Why didn't you warn me about this?
Even if we had, there's
nothing you can do.
Sure there is!
I'm gonna cover myself in
anti-ghost stuff! Usopp!
You gotta let me borrow stuff too!
Who's that?
What's that voice?
No! No!
It's a ghost ship!
We're gonna die!
This is the song of the jam! Hurry!
Cover your ears!
You'll be cursed!
If you talk back to the ghost then
you'll be pulled into the sea!
Don't answer them!
No matter what they say to you!
They'll steal your soul and
bind them to the ghost ship!
Who is that?
Is someone actually riding this ship?
So, can you cut ghosts?
On the deck, look.
Garden rumble of the crew It's
time to ship out Binks' brew
Why did it have to be me of all people?
I want a recount.
This is why I said I would go alone.
Yeah, that'd be great.
You'd go sailing off with a bunch of
skeletons, and we'd never see you again.
Should have made Usopp go.
Nami-Swan!
Don't you worry!
Your sweet prince is here to protect you!
Come on!
You were all excited about
finding a treasure ship before.
There is no way in hell
this is a treasure ship!
Look at it!
It's got singing skeletons!
Well, maybe he's the one guarding
all the awesome treasure.
Anyway, I'm going.
There he is!
Evil makes me gone! Out with you!
Let Luffy rest in peace!
Why, good afternoon, you!
Thank you all for stopping by.
You must excuse me for not
greeting you properly before.
I really was quite surprised.
It's been so many years, you see,
wandering these waters all alone.
I'm so used to ghost ships
that humans frightened me.
Quite ironic, isn't it?
Ah, but please come
inside and take a seat.
I'm sure you have many tales to share.
Look!
It can talk!
It's a singing, talking Afro-skeleton!
Well, I'll be damned.
Huh?
Oh, my.
What a charming young
woman you are. Beautiful.
Oh, no.
I'm all eyes for ladies like you.
Or I would be if skeletons had any eyes.
Yo-ho-ho-ho!
Could you perhaps show me
your panties? Yeah, right!
Feisty!
I like it!
That hurt me right down to the bone,
because I'm a skeleton, you see?
I got it!
That kick just gave him
swelling on his skull.
Hey, wait, do skeletons poop?
We've got like a million questions to
ask before that one! Oh, yes. I poop.
Haven't you ever heard of TMI?
We don't need to hear that! Anyway,
how is it that you can sing and talk
like that when you're nothing but bones?
Are you really the living dead or what?
Also, why are you here?
And what the hell happened to this ship?
These waters aren't
really haunted, are they?
We need answers. Hold on.
I got one for you. You ready?
Will you join our crew?
Yes.
Certainly.
Whoa!
It's such a pleasure to meet you.
Hello and good day to you all.
As of today, I will be joining you on
this ship as your newest crew member.
Once dead and all bones,
my name is Brooke and i
do hope we can get along
are you kidding me what the
heck is this thing oh my
what a tough crowd you are
please don't
haunt me my
goodness and what a lovely
young woman perhaps you
would like to show me
your panties that's enough
sexual harassment damn it
there's no way a walking
talking afro-sporting
skeleton could exist this
must be a dream we just need
to wake up oh it's a dream
literally that's nice uh excuse me
what is this thing and why is it on our
ship that's our new crew member isn't
he funny who cares he's not joining
our crew this is exactly why i want you
to go with him what the hell happened
were you just picking your noses while
he brought a skeleton back to the
ship i know we messed up now now
let's be civil everyone why don't we go
inside you can treat me to dinner you
don't get to decide that what a spacious
dining room you've got and such a splendid
kitchen a magnificent ship if i've
ever seen one yep of course it is It's
the most super ship I've ever made.
Those sockets look empty, but
you got a good eye for quality.
Franky, don't get friendly
with the skeleton.
Speaking of quality, I can't
wait to try out your cooking.
Since I was stuck on
that dreary ghost ship,
it's been decades since
I've eaten a proper meal.
I thought my stomach
shrink and shrink until
I couldn't even tell the back of my belly?
from the front of my back anymore.
That was the sort of miserable life I led.
Let me tell you, that's saying a lot,
seeing as skeletons don't even
have a proper back or stomach.
It's a skull joke!
I get it!
Let me say, I am quite the gentleman,
so I am well-versed in the art
of patiently waiting for my food,
no matter how long it takes. Yeah! No! No!
My dear boy, can I have a glass of milk?
It's good for the bones, they say.
Shut up, or I'm gonna smash your skull!
Oh, by the way, skeleton.
Sorry, but my name is Brooke.
Ah, but that reminds me.
I know this is rude, But I don't
believe I ever caught your name.
Oh, me?
My name is Luffy.
So anyway, what are you?
You invited him to join the crew
and you just now ask him that?
We can finish interrogating
the skeleton later.
For now, let's put all those
octopi you caught to good use.
Magical!
Go ahead and eat all of
this you want, Brooke!
Sanji's cooking is the
best of the whole world!
Although, my stomach is empty.
I think my heart has already been filled.
Don't cry.
I couldn't help but notice that
your portion is a bit large.
Would you be interested
in switching with me?
You can have seconds!
Just leave her alone!
The revive, revive fruit?
So it was a Devil Fruit after all.
It's a complicated tale.
The truth of the matter is, I actually
did die already many years ago.
Could you clean off your damn face?
I've never seen such a messy eater.
The revive, revive fruit.
allows a person to be
reanimated after they have died.
Even among Devil Fruit powers,
the ability to live two lives
is indeed quite strange.
You're a revive man!
Then you're not immortal.
It's more like you died once and it
gave you a second chance at life.
In short, yes. Ah, excuse me.
As I said, it's complicated.
But during my first life, if you
will, I was a pirate, just like you.
That explains the ship!
That it does.
Excuse me again.
I'm going to beat some
manners into you if I
have to break every
single one of your bones.
A long time ago,
I was sailing with the rest of my
crew through these accursed waters.
Now, for the record, I had flesh and
blood like anyone else back then.
At any rate, we had the misfortune of
running afoul of a very powerful adversary.
Soon the entire crew met its demise.
Of course that included me as well.
When I was alive the revive revive fruit
did precious little other than rob me of
my ability To swim but on that fateful
day its true power awakened as I lay dead.
My spirit returned from
the netherworld and
came to unite with this
body of mine once again.
Now if it had actually found my body as
intended that would all be well and good.
But as you can see the fog around here is
quite thick so the matter became a bit?
Complicated.
In short, poor little Soulbrook
couldn't find his way back home.
All in all, my spirit wandered
through the foggy waters,
searching for my body for an entire year.
Then, at the end of its tragic journey,
the two were reunited once again.
Much to my soul's dismay,
by the time it found my body, there was
nothing left but a miserable pile of bones.
I was so shocked my eyes were
as wide as dinner plates.
Not that I have eyes to begin with.
You got lost, huh?
So you're stupid just like Zoro?
Hey now!
And so a walking, talking
skeleton was born.
Man, those Devil Fruit powers
can be pretty scary sometimes!
Even though you're just bones, it
still brought you back to life.
Yeah, but it only does it once.
Despite the fact that he still
can't swim and he's stuck like this.
Seems kind of like a
crappy deal if you ask me?
Skeletons aren't supposed
to have hair, are they?
Especially not so much of it.
Is that Afro a wig or something?
No, my roots are just very strong.
I'll take your word for it.
Then that means you're not
actually a ghost after all?
You're just a normal human like us?
Well, normal is a
stretch, I suppose, but...
The important thing is that
you're definitely not a ghost!
Oh, heavens no, I hate ghosts!
If I saw one, I'd scream
my lungs out if I had any!
You're a skeleton and
you're afraid of ghosts?
Have you tried looking
in the mirror lately?
No mirrors!
What's wrong?
Hey, hold up!
What's going on here?
No, why?
Why can't we see you?
Why don't you show up in the mirror?
Are you for real?
That's awesome!
Look at his feet!
He doesn't even have a shadow!
You're right!
What kind of creature are you?
Don't take a tea break you better explain
yourself right away
mister I suppose that I
should tell you the
rest of the story about
what happened while I was drifting in this
evil sea and the second tragedy I was forced
to face what I told you about becoming
a skeleton is true but the reason I don't
have a shadow is a
different matter entirely
now my shadow was stolen someone took it
from me several years ago stolen but how
I guess that's not any more ridiculous
than a talking skeleton but it's still
hard to swallow can something like that
really happen yes I'm afraid it can and in
addition to losing my reflection having my
shadow stolen means I can no longer exist
in the world of light if even a ray of
sunlight touched this body every inch that
it fell upon would be reduced to naught
but ash
saw
someone
with the same curse
as me lose his mind and run into the
sunlight when at last his screams went
silent nothing was left but a pile of dust?
It was so frightful, I swear my soul
practically left my body a second time.
And just as the sunlight
does not cast my shadow,
my image cannot be reflected in a
mirror or captured in a photograph.
You must forgive me for startling you,
but I hope you can understand my
reluctance to share this story.
For as you see, not only have
all of my comrades been slain,
I also live in a world without light.
Well, I hate to say it, but
your life sure does suck.
Even still, right now,
I'm so happy to have it.
A fluffy afro, a big smile, the
cheery gentleman skeleton, Brooke.
Always a pleasure.
Where does all this optimism come from?
Hey, what's wrong?
He's flipping out.
What a wonderful day this has been.
I met other people.
Buried in a heavy fog,
even though I knew decades had passed,
I couldn't tell when one
day ended and another began.
Unable to navigate or steer the ship.
My companions long since dead.
I could only drift aimlessly.
And so I waited and waited.
As the waves rocked me back and forth.
You can't even imagine how
lonely I was all those years.
Not just lonely, but scared.
Wanting to die every single day.
Even still a long life is
a blessing not a curse.
You've made me so happy meeting such
wonderful people gives my life meaning.
If I had but the eyes to shed them,
I would be crying tears of happiness.
Right now I was happy beyond measure
when you asked me to join your
crew and I sincerely want to thank
you from the bottom of my heart.
However I fear that I must
decline your offer. What?
Why would you do that?
As I mentioned to all of you just now?
My shadow has been stolen from me.
and I am unable to come in
contact with any sunlight.
Lonely though I may be, for
now I am able to survive.
thanks to the thick fog
covering these seas.
However, if I were to go on a journey with
you, it would only be a matter of time?
before I met my unfortunate demise.
Therefore,
however unlikely it may be, I'll wait for
the day when my shadow can be restored.
Make no bones about it. No!
I don't want to hear you
make excuses like that.
If you need your shadow back so
bad, then we'll get it back for you.
You said someone stole it from you, right?
Who was it?
Where can we find them?
Thank you.
You truly are a kind person, aren't you?
But for that reason, I'm
afraid that I cannot tell you.
We've only just met, you see.
And I cannot ask you
to throw your life away
attempting something
that's nearly impossible.
I'm sure the guy's tough and
all, but give me a break.
You got nothing to lose.
Least you can do is tell us his name.
No, it's best that I don't.
Besides, I doubt I could find him anyway.
But I have decided that when
and if I do ever reach him,
I will fight him to
the death of my shadow.
I don't know when my second life will end,
but I am willing to wait for
him for the rest of my days.
But never mind that.
Why don't I play a song for you?
I am skilled with a great
many instruments, you know.
When I sailed the seas with my
old crew, I was their musician.
What?
Are you serious?
Our crew needs a musician.
Hurry up and join us already.
I'm begging you. No.
I haven't played music for
anyone in years, but here goes.
Hey, what's wrong?
You're freaking out.
Ghost!
Wait!
Get up!
It's leaving
What?
Something's happening
to the ship It can't be.
A terrible fortune.
We must have been watching them.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
Everyone look to the front.
That noise we heard was
this gate slamming shut.
Our passage has already been blocked off.
It seems this is the backside
of the gate. That bad?
This is very bad
Come to the rear of the ship!
Hurry!
What in the world is that?
Did you by any chance pick up a barrel
from the waters on your way here?
Yeah we did it was a trap you're
all in great danger simply
put your ship's been targeted
ever since you came here you
mean there's someone out there
hunting us down and by the
way how'd we run into that gate
when our ship's not moving?
Where the heck did that
creepy island come from this
is the ghost island that
wanders throughout these seas.
They call it Thriller Ball.
Hey, this is strange.
The lock pose isn't reacting
to this island at all.
Nor should it,
because originally this island came
all the way in from the West Blue.
Truly, this has been a
fortunate day for me.
Not only was I able to meet you, but
now my wish has been granted as well.
That's a hell of a jump.
Yes, there's no pesky
flesh weighing me down.
Please do not follow me.
You must break through that gate
behind you and escape this place.
Whatever you do, you cannot
drop your anchor in here.
That being said, it truly was a
pleasure meeting all of you today.
I won't forget your
kindness so long as I live.
Farewell.
I hope we meet again on the high seas.
He broke weight.
Isn't he a Devil Fruit user?
Then he's gonna sink like a rock!
He's running on the water!
That is too cool!
Uh, anyway, Luffy, we should
listen to him and get moving.
I don't really understand the situation
here, but I do know this island is bad news.
Huh?
You guys say something?
He totally wants to go!
Thank you.